To be good at pelvic rotation in forward carving,
We've put a lot of effort into it.
Faster, more accurate, more powerful.
In my personal style, I only use my shoulders.
Ultimately, heel side turn to toe side turn.
This is a series of seasonal lessons.
Make sure you watch the previous videos.
I highly recommend you to practice in order.
If you don't have the equipment set up or practice the previous process,
it may not have any effect.
Hello, I'm Kim Seung Won.
Now, this is the seventh time.
"ep7 Counter Rotation"
I will teach you about counter rotation.
It's exactly the counter rotation to use when entering the turn on the toe side turn.
Maybe the term count rotation is
I'm sure some of you are a little unfamiliar.
Let me briefly explain the rotation and counter rotation.
"Rotation and Counter Rotation"
In case of rotation, the direction of progress of the turn,
For example, in the case of a heel side turn, proceed in this direction.
When proceeding in the left direction on a regular style
If you return your upper body in the direction of progress, (Motion)
This is called rotation.
In case of toe side turn, a regular style is proceed to the right.
If you have this rotation of the upper body in this direction (Motion)
This is called rotation.
Counter rotation is the opposite of rotation. In the case of heel side turn
We're not turning the upper body this way.
If you turn it the other way around... (Motion)
In the case of toe side turn
The opposite direction of rotation direction is called counter rotation. (Motion)
I'm sure you've used a lot of rotations in Slidington.
Let me explain a little bit about the rotation difference between Slidington and Carvington.
First of all, rotation in Carvington is basically used a lot in heel side turns.
After entering the turn at the heel side turn,
I tell you to lead the upper body. (Motion)
I'm telling you to lead your upper body.
Lead is the action of returning
the upper body in the direction of the turn. (Motion)
When this looked at me from the outside,
i've been giving you the turn direction, but (Motion)
Actually, from the outside, (Motion)
I'm not going to rotate it around the deck, I'm not going to turn it around.
Because it doesn't look like it's turning (Motion)
It's commonly referred to as the sychronous rotation.
Actually, from the outside, it doesn't seem like he's doing rotation,
Most people (Motion)
ride themselves as if they were feel rotation.
In case of counter rotation,
In Slidington, it's usually says kicking backwards is a bad habit but
In Caving, especially toe side turns, it be one of the key technologies that's very important.
Of course, it's not a must because we rode well without the counter rotation that we've done so far but
It is a technology that can quickly open and enter the pelvis when entering the toe side turn.
"Why do I do counter-tions?"
If we think about it,
To be good at pelvic rotation in forward carving,
We've put a lot of effort into it.
When you do heel side turn, you open your pelvis and enter. and (Motion)
Lead the upper body while stretching the front legs and maintaining the pelvis. (Motion)
And push the pelvis into the slope first in the toe side turn, (Motion)
And raise your arms to create an outer diameter, (Motion)
In a way, these things...
I'm trying to keep my pelvis on the deck.
In addition to this, if you do counter rotation in toe side turn,
If I could show you a counter rotation demonstration,
From the side,
After the heel side turn, While the turn enters (Motion)
Turn the upper body outward in the direction of the turn (Motion)
By returning it, the pelvis is rotated stronger (Motion)
If you push your pelvis in that state, (Motion)
A random BBP Posture is
you can enter in a very good Posture, but (Motion)
We're going to put more into this state. (Motion)
If we rotate the pelvis more (Motion)
It's much more advantageous for push your pelvis in.(Motion)
In short, the counter rotation at the toe side turn is
Faster, more accurate, more powerful
you can push your pelvis and create an outer diameter Posture
it's a technique like that.
So, on the contrary,
In the case of heel side turn,
Some people might wonder if counter rotation is used.
Heel side turns Different rider may have different ideas.
In my opinion, in case of heel side turn, when we did edge change at toe side turn,
The upper body sometimes closes like this during the process of reading the upper body. (Motion)
If the upper body is re-open when closed, (Motion)
because the deck can go around and create an unstable turn,
when heel side turn edge chasing was said to have made a slight mistake in the toe side turn,
in other words, if you entered with closed,
Close your shoulders with the counter and enter the heel side turn. (Motion)
And then you open your upper body again. (Motion)
I think I can ride that way.
But in the case of heel side turn, if possible.
Edge change as clean as possible from toe side turn.
so when landing, the upper body is open to enter the turn.
I think it's much more advantageous.
That's why the technology of counter rotation itself,
basically, it is better to use it only for entering the toe side turn.
That's what I think.
"How to do a counter-tation"
I'm going to explain to you about counter-rotation.
I showed you a little bit earlier.
I think what's important here is continuity in heel side turn.
Of course, it can be difficult when you're a beginner.
Let me explain how beginners do it first.
In case of toe side turn, the upper body is this open in the neutral position on the toe (Motion)
you're going to get the edging, and then take turn like this.
It feels like the upper body just stays in the direction while making a turn. (Motion)
It doesn't feel like I'll begin after opening the upper body.
When I am edging and the turn progresses, (Motion)
The direction you looked at when the upper body was first edged, (Motion)
It's easy to think that it feels like you're going in while maintaining the direction. (Motion)
So I'm going into the neutral position, (Motion)
and then, entering with the upper body opened, (Motion)
and then, this is how the upper body gets more and more twisted. (Motion)
When no more twisted, (Motion)
it will proceed as it is. (Motion)
Beginners, like this.
It's okay if you to go in like this from the start of the turn. But
Ultimately, it is best to connect naturally from the heel side turn to the toe side turn.
We've learned how to do it when we're Up-unweight turn before.
When you're up, you're giving it a little lean-out and
by lifting the outer shoulder, (Motion)
While do Edge-changing, (Motion)
the motion of raising the arm and then the movement of rotation and edge switching, (Motion)
it should be connected naturally that.
(Motion)
Once more.. When edge switching while heel side turn ,(Motion)
it will be made Edge-changing by angulation, (Motion)
then entering.. with doing motions in a natural continuity.. (Motion)
I think this continuity is very important.
If we ride it later, it could be connected naturally.
It's good to start by pivoting the upper body into the toe side turn as a practice. (Motion)
But, ultimately, think of it as doing while from a heel side turn to a toe side turn. (Motion)
hand gestures don't really matter at this time.
Throw your right arm forward and (Motion)
it doesn't matter if you twist your left arm back like this.
In the course of practice, you do twist your body as much as you can. (Motion)
It's a good idea to turn your arms around like this, but (Motion)
In my personal style, if I get used to counter rotation later,
Rather than overspinning your arm like this (Motion)
In my personal style, I only use my shoulders.
I prefer to go in from the heel side turn and use only one's shouldersto enter.
That is, arms don't matter.
Eventually (Motion) transmitted through the upper body to the pelvis,
because it's a technique for twisting pelvis after all (Motion)
It's not necessarily about turning your arms around.
It doesn't mean anything if the pelvis doesn't turn and only the arms like this. (Motion)
Eventually, it's important to turn your arms around, turn your shoulders around, and connect them to your pelvis.
Ultimately, you don't have to turn your arms around (Motion)
In my case, I'm riding a style where I just turn my shoulders and get excited at the counter. (Motion)
People who've seen a lot of my videos know that,
In my case, I like simple and neat Riding style.
so that's how I'm riding it's how I ride it.
You can't say this is the answer.
I think you can make an arm shape in the style you want.
Now, I'll show you a demonstration on the slope.
"Slop Demonstration"
Counter rotation...
I'm going to show you how to enter the counter rotation from the toe side turn.
As I told you earlier, Beginners in the process of raising it up at heel side turn
Because it can be a little unnatural and awkward to move on to the toe,
Initially, you use the upper body and arms to forced the toe neutral Posture in the counter (Motion)
and, in the direction of the fence you saw when you entered the turn, It goes into the feeling of maintaining the upper body.
I think it could be a key point.
First of all, I'll do my best doing raising it up from heel side turn it as easy as possible for beginners to follow.
I'll try to ride it.
heel side turn goes in, doing down as he practiced before.
From Neutral (Motion)
Hit it, (Motion)
Again.
Get in.
From Neutral
at the counter
Heel again.
In the Neutral
Counter
Heel~
Keep your upper body and eyes open with the fence you were looking at in the neutral section.
You can use the open pelvis allows for stronger external diameter.
It was a little too fast, so it wasn't easy to show you
because I got on a little slope.
You're a little bit... gentle. Practice on a gentle slope.
Open the upper body in the neutral section when crossing the heel to toe (Motion)
The upper body keeps looking at the fence that I looked at then. (Motion)
If you keep your gaze in the direction of the actual turn and enter the turn, (Motion)
I think you can learn counter rotation more easily.
Next time, I'll show you the natural connection from Heel to Toe.
Take a look.
This time, as I said before, I'm going to go up from heel to toe.
I'll show you how the counter rotation works naturally.
You're going to do a lot of Edgecanging by raising your arms like you're giving the outside diameter when you're on a heel side turn.
It naturally connects the movement to the movement that leads to the counter rotation.
Let me show you.
I'm going to turn my arms a little bit too much than I normally do.
I'm leaving.
Heel~
Edgechanging
Counter
Enter
Heel~
Edgechanging, counter~
Heel again.
Heel... Edgechange.. Counter...
Okay, Like this, from Heel Edgechanging to Counter rotation
With a natural connection
If you ride like this, you can press it you'll find a more natural, faster, more powerful counter-rotation
That's about it.
Thank you for your efforts.